http://www.donheights.ca/privacy-policy/

Don Heights Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletters. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve the user experience. Your information helps us to respond to and improve your customer service requests and support needs.
To process transactions.
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company or organization for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic emails.
The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your request or order.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email in compliance with CASL (Canadian Anti-Spam Legislation).
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and who are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, protect ours or others rights, property or safety. We do not provide non-personally identifiable visitor information to any other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.
Third Party Links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on March 16, 2017.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us at office@donheights.ca.
Search for:
Event Calendar
SeptemberOctober 2020November
MOTUWETHFRSASU
2829301234Events for October 1stNo EventsEvents for October 2ndNo EventsEvents for October 3rdNo EventsEvents for October 4th 10:30 am - 12:00 pmSunday Service on Zoom password 1111 (click for details)ZOOM meeting567891011Events for October 5thNo EventsEvents for October 6thNo EventsEvents for October 7thNo EventsEvents for October 8thNo EventsEvents for October 9thNo EventsEvents for October 10thNo EventsEvents for October 11th 10:30 am - 12:00 pmSunday Service on Zoom password 1111 (click for details)ZOOM meeting12131415161718Events for October 12thNo EventsEvents for October 13thNo EventsEvents for October 14thNo EventsEvents for October 15thNo EventsEvents for October 16thNo EventsEvents for October 17thNo EventsEvents for October 18th 10:30 am - 12:00 pmSunday Service on Zoom password 1111 (click for details)ZOOM meeting19202122232425Events for October 19thNo EventsEvents for October 20thNo EventsEvents for October 21stNo EventsEvents for October 22ndNo EventsEvents for October 23rdNo EventsEvents for October 24thNo EventsEvents for October 25th 10:30 am - 12:00 pmSunday Service on Zoom password 1111 (click for details)ZOOM meeting2627282930311
Events for October 26thNo EventsEvents for October 27thNo EventsEvents for October 28thNo EventsEvents for October 29thNo EventsEvents for October 30thNo EventsEvents for October 31stNo Events
Donate to Don Heights
Click image to donateto
Don Heights
Don Heights Bulletin
Click here to view and downloadour monthly Bulletin
Don Heights Songbook
Click here to orderthe Don Heights Songbook
Sign-up for our weekly eNewsletter to keep up-to-date with all of our activities
Subscribe to our mailing list
Like us on Facebook
Facebook
Our Location
Subscribe Today!
© 2017-2019 DON HEIGHTS UNITARIAN CONGREGATION | ALL RIGHTS RESERVED | PRIVACY POLICY | NUPLANET DIGITAL
